accessconsciousness.com 2018-12-05

# Privacy Policy | Access Consciousness

  1. Home
  2. Policies

* * *

## ACCESS CONSCIOUSNESS PRIVACY POLICY

_Last updated: April 24, 2018._

Access Consciousness knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting Access Consciousness, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

Regarding our compliance with the European Data Protection Act 2018, please review our Data Protection Declaration.

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Access Consciousness Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your Access Consciousness experience. Here are the types of information we gather.

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, marketing, and communicating with you. You accept herewith that your information is stored, used and passed on within all Access Consciousness companies (Access Consciousness USA, Access Consciousness Europe and Access Consciousness Australia). We herewith confirm that a Data Protection Agreement is in place and no data will be used other than authorized by you by each company.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Access Consciousness or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Access Consciousness on other Web sites.
  * **Mobile:** When you download or use apps created by Access Consciousness or our subsidiaries, partners or agents, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services.
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Access Consciousness if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your preferences.
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

### Does Access Consciousness Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries, partners or agents that each of the three Access Consciousness companies (Access Consciousness USA, Access Consciousness Europe and Access Consciousness Australia) control that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

  * **Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Access Consciousness customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your Preferences.
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Access Consciousness, LLC, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Protection of Access Consciousness and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Access Consciousness, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### Which Information Can I Access?

Access Consciousness gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Access Consciousness for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

### What Choices Do I Have?

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Access Consciousness features as your profile, wish lists, customer reviews, and testimonials.
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Preferences. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Access Consciousness, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)
  * The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Access Consciousness's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Access Consciousness products and services that require you to Sign in.

### Are Children Allowed to Use Access Consciousness?

Access Consciousness does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Access Consciousness products or attend seminars only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Access Consciousness, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas. If you have any concern about privacy at Access Consciousness, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current **Privacy Policy** applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

### Does Access Consciousness Use Cookies?

This policy explains how we use cookies and related technologies (collectively called “Cookies”) to provide our services to you through our website http://accessconsciousness.com (the “Site”). By accessing or using our Site you consent to our use of Cookies in the manner described in this policy. Please do not use our Site if you are not comfortable with the ways in which we use Cookies.

### What is a Cookie?

Cookies are small text files sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while the user is browsing a website. When a user visits a website more than once, the browser sends Cookies back to the website, allowing the website to recognize the user and remember things like their personalized details and preferences. More information about Cookies and details of how to manage or disable them can be found on aboutcookies.org.

### Do we use Cookies?

Yes. We may obtain information about your prior visits to our site or whether you entered our Site from an affiliate website by using Cookies that are typically stored on the hard drive of your computer or on your mobile device.

### When do we use Cookies?

We use Cookies when you create a user account with us and when you navigate our Site. For example, when you return to our Site after logging in, Cookies provide information to our Site so that the Site remembers you. Cookies help us to improve our Site, and to deliver a better, more personalized service.

### What types of Cookies do we use?

We mainly use Cookies to make our services work and to improve our services. We currently use Cookies for the following purposes:  
Operation of our service: We use Cookies to monitor login, session and status data. This allows us to know, for example, if you are logged in or not. We also use Cookies to remember if you have seen our cookie banner and to remember if you have logged in previously. We use Cookies to remember what items you place in your shopping cart when purchasing goods or services through our Site.  
Security: We use Cookies to enable and support our security features, and to help us detect malicious activity and violations of our **Terms& Conditions.**  
Preferences: We use temporary “session” cookies which enables your web browser to remember which pages on our Site have already been visited. This information may be used to help us to improve, administer and diagnose problems with our Site and server. Our Site may also use other technical methods to track visitor usage, including web beacons. (“Web beacons” are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of a website.) We may also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our Site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Site. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us, or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf.

### Third Party Cookies

Some Cookies that have been set on our Site may not be related to or controlled by us. When you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, Twitter or Facebook, these service providers may set their own Cookies on your web browser. We do not control the use of these Cookies and cannot access them due to the way Cookies work, as Cookies can only be accessed by the party which originally set them. You should check the third party’s website for more information about these Cookies.

### How to refuse the use of Cookies

You can change your web browser settings so your computer warns you each time a Cookie is sent, or to turn off all Cookies. Each browser is a little different, so please look at your browser "help menu" to learn the correct way to modify your Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies you won't have access to many features that may make your browsing of our Site and use of our services smoother, and some of our services may not function properly or at all. For example, if you disable Cookies you will not be able to login to your user account, or make an online purchase.

### Visitors outside the United States

Our Website and the servers that make this Website available worldwide are located in the United States. The Internet laws in the United States govern all matters relating to this Website. Any information you provide in subscribing to our Website or registering or ordering at our Website will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our Website and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing and use.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding our use of Cookies or privacy policy please contact us.
